Alexander Lundquist

Location: Stockholm, Sweden

Email: alexander.lundquist@hyperisland.se

Phone: +46 709 55 8187

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-lundquist-b16b48164/

My Experience

Former World / Europe Cup Ski Cross Athlete looking to combine my passion to achieve long term goals with my studies in Software development. Leveraging my competitive background, I co-founded and managed a thriving wholesale business, achieving a recurring revenue of over 300,000kr.

I bring a unique perspective to software development, blending my entrepreneurial skills with technical expertise in both front-end and back-end.

My commitment to achieving long-term goals, honed on the slopes, translates seamlessly into my passion for software development. In addition to my formal education, I continually refine my skills through personal projects, demonstrating my dedication to staying at the forefront of the tech industry.

More information about my personal projects can be found on my personal website as well as Github.

Core Skills

- C#, ASP.NET, RESTfull Apis, Html, css, Javascript, React.
- Experience in achieving long term goals
- Entrepreneurship
- Communication and presentation skills

Alexander Lundquist

Location: Stockholm, Sweden

Email: alexander.lundquist@hyperisland.se

Phone: +46 709 55 8187

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-lundquist-b16b48164/

Career Summary

January 2023 - Present

December 2022 - January 2024

Drivhuset

Business Developer

Outline

Responsible for leading the Stockholm office on Drivhuset part. Drivhuset is a start-up incubator for students looking to start their first business. Jobs includes one on one coaching sessions with aspiring entrepreneurs in their early development stage. In addition to facilitating entrepreneurial workshops and being a public speaker for youth entrepreneurship. Having over 200+ client one on one meeting throughout

January 2022 - Present De jounge & Lundquist AB
Co-Funder

Outline

Co-founded a successful wholesale business for food delicacies, specializing in the import and distribution of "Kalix Löjrom" caviar. Managed all aspects of the business, including sales, marketing, and logistics. Achieved a recurring revenue of over 300k SEK,

November 2019 - November 2021 Churchill Arms Waiter

Outline

Waiter at Churchill Arms serving food and beverage to finance professional athletic career.

September 2019 - November 2021 Sollentuna Slalomklubb

Alexander Lundquist

Location: Stockholm, Sweden

Email: alexander.lundquist@hyperisland.se

Phone: +46 709 55 8187

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-lundquist-b16b48164/

Ski Coach for youth

Outline

Ski coach for children aged 12-16 years old looking to pursue a professional ski career. Responsible for 25 youths while traveling abroad and to follow their developments through the year.

June 2016 - August 2018

Kungliga Svenska Segel Sällskapet Group Manager & Sailing instructor

Outline

Responsible for children aged 10-14 years old during sailing camp in Stockholm Archipelago. Also to supervise fellow sailing instructors to ensure great communication, development and inclusion for everyone involved.

Education & Qualifications

- Hyper Island, AI Business Consultant
- Torsby Alpina Skidgymnasium with specialization in Alpine Skiing
- Chas Academy, Full Stack .Net Developer